A Guide to the Papers of Hugh Scott 1681-1917
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- TOPICAL
  - V.I.P. Correspondence 1952-1986, n.d., 2 folders (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence to Marian Scott 1955-1979 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Howard H. Baker, Jr. 1978-1987 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: George Bush 1979-1987 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Jimmy Carter 1978 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Winston S. Churchill 1952 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Dwight D. Eisenhower (including his address to Republican leaders in Philadelphia, inscribed to Hugh Scott) and Mamie Doud Eisenhower 1954-1960 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Gerald R. Ford 1977-1986 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Mark O. Hatfield 1981-1987 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Hubert H. Humphrey 1965 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Edward M. Kennedy 1977-1981 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Charles McC. Mathias, Jr. 1979-1986 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Richard M. Nixon 1956, 1960 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Franklin D. Roosevelt 1940 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Arlen Specter 1980-1985 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Ted Stevens 1979-1983 (Box 17)
  - V.I.P. Correspondence: Richard L. Thornburgh 1979-1986 (Box 17)
  - The Virginia Museum of Fine Arts: Collector of the Year 1967-1969 (Box 17)
  - Woman's Medical College of Pennsylvania 1954-1960 (Box 17)
  - Writing Class Essays by Marian Huntington Chase Scott [1961] (Box 17)
  - "Your Senator's Report": Transcripts of Programs done by Hugh Scott 1970-1976 (Box 17)
  - Youth for Understanding 1979-1982 (Box 17)
- INVITATIONS
  - Acceptances 1960-1975 (Box 18)
  - Acceptances--January 1966 1965-1966 (Box 18)
  - Acceptances--February - March 1966 1966, 4 folders (Box 18)
  - Acceptances--April - September 1966 1966, 6 folders (Box 19)
  - Acceptances--October - November 1966 1966, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Acceptances--January - February 1972 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Acceptances--March - July 1972 1972, 6 folders (Box 21)
  - Acceptances--August - December 1972 1972, 6 folders (Box 22)
  - Acceptances--January - March 1973 1972-1973, 6 folders (Box 23)
  - Acceptances--April - July 1973 1973 (Box 24)
  - Acceptances--September 1973 1973, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Acceptances--November - December 1973 1973, 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Acceptances--Itinerary 1974 1974 (Box 25)
  - Acceptances--January 1974 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - Acceptances--February 1974 1974 (Box 25)
  - Acceptances--March - July 1974 1974, 5 folders (Box 26)
  - Acceptances--August - December 1974 1974, 5 folders (Box 27)
  - Schedules 1972, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Schedules 1973 (Box 27)
  - Schedules 1973 (Box 28)
  - Schedules 1974, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Schedules 1975, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Schedules 1976, 2 folders (Box 28)
- BOOKS BY HUGH SCOTT
  - Come to the Party: Drafts 1 and 2 [1965], 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Acknowledgments, Foreword, Preface, Epilogue, and Outlines [1967] (Box 29)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter on "Campaign for the White House" [1967] (Box 30)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter on "Campaigns," and related [1967], 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Capitol Hill" [1967], 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Elwood, Indiana to Wall Street" [1967], 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "The Future of the Party" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Not Quite Washington" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapters "Philadelphia I and II" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Phoenix to Ashes" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "The Republic" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "The Road Back" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "San Francisco--The Unpacific City" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Scranton" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "The Senate: In and Out" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Virginia and Pennsylvania" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "Washington, Philadelphia and Albany" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of the Chapter "The White House" [1967] (Box 31)
  - Come to the Party: Draft Two n.d., 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Come to the Party: Early drafts of miscellaneous chapters, and related [1967] (Box 32)
  - Come to the Party: Anecdotes and Recollections 1965-1966, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Come to the Party: Correspondence 1965-1968 (Box 32)
  - Come to the Party: Correspondence re books donated to Pennsylvania Colleges 1968 (Box 32)
  - Come to the Party: Correspondence with Albert N. Leman 1967 (Box 32)
  - Come to the Party: Correspondence with Prentice-Hall, Inc. 1965-1968 (Box 33)
  - Come to the Party: Memoranda 1965-1968 (Box 33)
  - Come to the Party: Printed Material 1968 (Box 33)
  - Come to the Party: Thank you's from Political V.I.P.s 1968 (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China: Typed Drafts with Autograph Revisions n.d. (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China:: Second Page Proofs n.d. (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China: Third Page Proofs n.d. (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China: Fourth Page Proofs 1966 (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China: Index n.d. (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China: Correspondence re book 1967-1973 (Box 33)
  - The Golden Age of China: Correspondence re books donated to Pennsylvania Colleges 1967 (Box 34)
  - The Golden Age of China: Correspondence re books purchased, and related papers 1967 (Box 34)
  - The Golden Age of China: Correspondence with Henry Trubner 1965-1973 (Box 34)
  - The Golden Age of China: Correspondence with Charles E. Tuttle Co., Inc. 1963-1966, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - The Golden Age of China: Memoranda 1964-1967 (Box 34)
  - The Golden Age of China: Miscellaneous Drafts and Revisions 1965, n.d. (Box 34)
  - The Golden Age of China: Publicity 1967 (Box 34)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Draft n.d. (Box 34)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Draft n.d. (Box 34)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Draft One n.d. (Box 34)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Drafts Two and Three n.d., 2 folders (Box 35)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Draft Four n.d. (Box 35)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Late Draft 1973, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Correspondence re Publicaton 1973-1975 (Box 36)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Illustrations n.d. (Box 36)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Notes by Hugh Scott n.d. (Box 36)
  - The Joy of Collecting: Questionnaires sent to Senators 1973 (Box 36)
- PHOTOGRAPHS: TOPICAL
  - Campaign for Presidency: Thomas E. Dewey 1948 (Box 36)
  - Campaign for U.S. Senator 1958, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - China 1970, 1972 (Box 36)
  - China 1972, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - China 1972 (Box 37)
  - England Tour [1970] (Box 37)
  - Indonesia: Commonwealth Parliamentary Union 1959 (Box 37)
  - Japan-U.S. Parliamentary Exchange Conference 1969 (Box 37)
  - King and Queen of Sikkim 1971 (Box 37)
  - Korea 1968 (Box 37)
  - Naval Service 1946-1954, n.d. (Box 37)
  - Naval Service: Iceland 1941 (Box 37)
  - Naval Service: Japan 1945 (Box 37)
  - Naval Service: Philippines 1945 (Box 37)
  - Naval Service: Philippines and Japan 1945 (Box 38)
  - Naval Service: Ship Collision 1945 (Box 38)
  - S. S. Hawkeye Mariner 1953 (Box 38)
  - United States Naval Academy, Annapolis, Maryland 1948 (Box 38)
  - University of Virginia Class of 1922 1957 (Box 38)
- PHOTOGRAPHS: HUGH & MARIAN SCOTT
  - Hugh Scott 1959-1982, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Marian Huntington Chase Scott 1959-1975, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Marian Scott: Ladies of the Senate and Republican Women 1968-1975 (Box 38)
  - Hugh and Marian Scott at social engagements n.d. (Box 38)
  - Hugh and Marian Scott on vacation in Europe 1951 (Box 38)
  - Hugh and Marian Scott with family and friends 1951, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Hugh and Marian Scott with various persons 1928-1986, 5 folders (Box 39)
  - Hugh and Marian Scott with various persons n.d., 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Hugh and Marian Scott with various persons n.d. (Box 40)
- PHOTOGRAPHS: VIPs
  - George and Barbara Bush n.d. (Box 40)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower 1951-1961, n.d. (Box 40)
  - Gerald R. and Betty Ford 1968-1976 (Box 40)
  - Lyndon Baines and Lady Bird Johnson 1965 (Box 40)
  - Richard M. and Patricia Nixon 1959-1973, n.d. (Box 40)
  - Ronald Reagan 1981-1984 (Box 40)
  - Scenes of Hong Kong, Japan, Korea, and the Philippines n.d., Slides; 2 folders (Box 40)
- PRINTED
  - Printed re Hugh and Marian Scott 1930-1987, n.d., 4 folders (Box 41)
  - Printed Government Documents 1973-1983 (Box 42)
  - Printed Government Documents: Tributes to the Honorable Hugh Scott...upon the occasion of his Retirement... 1976 (Box 42)
  - Printed Miscellaneous 1977, n.d. (Box 42)
  - Republican Fact-Book 1948, 1952 (Box 42)
- BOUND VOLUMES
  - Appointment Book 1969 (Box 43)
  - Appointment Book 1970, 2 volumes (Box 43)
  - Appointment Book, kept by William F. Hildebrand 1971 (Box 43)
  - Appointment Book 1971 (Box 44)
  - Appointment Book--July-December 1972 (Box 44)
  - China Trip: "NOTES From the Mansfield-Scott Trip to China" 1972 (Box 44)
  - China Trip: Photograph Scrapbook presented by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Republic of China 1969-1970 (Box 44)
  - "The Devil's Caravan" by Wheaton and Cooley 1972 (Box 45)
  - Eisenhower Club Manual 1951 (Box 45)
  - Guest Book for the National Chairman's Homecoming Dinner, August 28, 1948 1948 (Box 45)
  - Guest Book 1956-1974 (Box 45)
  - Guest Book 1970-1976 (Box 45)
  - Notebook containing field and survey notes by Hugh Scott at Randolph Macon College; and, notes on Spanish lessons 1918-1919 (Box 45)
  - Notebook kept during the Korean War by Hugh Scott 1950 (Box 45)
  - Pennsylvania State Planning Board: County Election Statistics 1970, 6 folders (Box 46)
  - Travel Books: Foreign Language Dictionaries 1929-1972 (Box 47)
  - Travel Books: Passports of Hugh and Marian Scott 1969-1970 (Box 48)
  - Travel Journal of a trip through the United States and Canada, kept by an unidentified person, February-June 1928 1928 (Box 48)
  - U. S. Naval Photographs of Hugh Scott and others, presented by Vice Admiral Charles D. Griffin, Commander Seventh Fleet 1960 (Box 48)
  - West Chester University Honors Hugh Scott 1987 (Box 48)
  - University of Virginia Memory Book, including memorabilia from other schools 1914-1921 (Box 49)
  - (Box 49)
  - University of Virginia Memory Book: loose memorabilia removed from scrapbook 1917-1922, n.d. (Box 49)
- LOOSE BOUND VOLUMES, These are oversized volumes.
  - "China before Marco Polo," Chinese dinner and lecture, October 23, 1978: Photographs 1978
  - Defense Supply Agency: Defense Personnel Support Center Dining-Out, February 10, 1973: Photographs 1973
  - U.S.S. Philadelphia keel laid August 12, 1972: Photographs 1972
  - U.S.S. Philadelphia launched October 19, 1974: Photographs 1974
  - World War II: Scrapbook of newspaper clippings re Japan Surrender, June-August 1945 1945